<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>rSVDdpd Homepage on rSVDdpd Website</title>
    <link>http://example.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content in rSVDdpd Homepage on rSVDdpd Website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="http://example.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Stream 1</title>
      <link>http://example.org/uhctd/stream1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/uhctd/stream1/</guid>
      <description>Video Stream 1 comprises of a small part of the video surveillance footage in Day 2 from Camera B in the UHCT Dataset. Some of the frames have been tampered with random image partially. It demonstrates the effect of these camera tampering on the estimated foreground.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stream 2</title>
      <link>http://example.org/uhctd/stream2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/uhctd/stream2/</guid>
      <description>Video Stream 2 comprises of a small part of the nighttime video surveillance footage in Day 1 from Camera A in the UHCT Dataset. Some of the frames have been tampered with random image partially. It demonstrates the effect of these camera tampering on the estimated foreground in the gray colour scale.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stream 3</title>
      <link>http://example.org/uhctd/stream3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/uhctd/stream3/</guid>
      <description>Video Stream 3 comprises of a small part of a daytime video surveillance footage in Day 1 from Camera A in the UHCT Dataset. Some of the frames have been tampered with random image partially. There is also presence of change in intensity and illumination due to the position of the sun.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stream 4</title>
      <link>http://example.org/uhctd/stream4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/uhctd/stream4/</guid>
      <description>Video Stream 4 comprises of a small part of a daytime video surveillance footage in Day 2 from Camera A in the UHCT Dataset. After some time, the camera has been tampered by moving it to point in a different direction. A reliable foreground extraction and background modelling algorithm should be sensitive to this rapid change in background and should indicate the presence of camera tampering.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video 112</title>
      <link>http://example.org/bmcdata/112/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/bmcdata/112/</guid>
      <description>Video 112 from BMC Dataset corresponds to a clear noiseless video of a street along with some moving cars in different locations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video 122</title>
      <link>http://example.org/bmcdata/122/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/bmcdata/122/</guid>
      <description>Video 122 from BMC Dataset corresponds to a clear noiseless video of a rotary along with moving cars.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video 212</title>
      <link>http://example.org/bmcdata/212/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/bmcdata/212/</guid>
      <description>Video 212 from BMC Dataset is similar to Video 112 but with a slight imperceptible noise in the pixel values added.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video 222</title>
      <link>http://example.org/bmcdata/222/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/bmcdata/222/</guid>
      <description>Video 222 from BMC Dataset is similar to Video 122 but with a slight imperceptible noise in the pixel values added.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video 312</title>
      <link>http://example.org/bmcdata/312/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/bmcdata/312/</guid>
      <description>Video 312 from BMC Dataset is similar to Video 112 but with varying illumination due to the movement of the sun.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video 322</title>
      <link>http://example.org/bmcdata/322/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/bmcdata/322/</guid>
      <description>Video 322 from BMC Dataset is similar to Video 122 but with varying illumination due to the movement of the sun.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video 412</title>
      <link>http://example.org/bmcdata/412/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/bmcdata/412/</guid>
      <description>Video 412 from BMC Dataset is similar to Video 112 but with an effect of cloud and presence of fog for a brief span of time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video 422</title>
      <link>http://example.org/bmcdata/422/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/bmcdata/422/</guid>
      <description>Video 422 from BMC Dataset is similar to Video 122 but with an effect of cloud and presence of fog for a brief span of time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video 512</title>
      <link>http://example.org/bmcdata/512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/bmcdata/512/</guid>
      <description>Video 512 from BMC Dataset is similar to Video 112 but with natural movement of the trees in the background.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video 522</title>
      <link>http://example.org/bmcdata/522/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/bmcdata/522/</guid>
      <description>Video 522 from BMC Dataset is similar to Video 122 but with natural movement of the trees in the background.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
